Vibhor Sharma

Full Stack Web Developer



≥ eminenceindia324@gmail.com

+91-8899234007 Mathura, UP

▶ Portfolio



Education Detail

Full Stack Web Development, **Masai School**

07/2022 - 03/2023 | In Progress

B.Tech(Electrical Engineering), **GLA University, Mathura**

07/2011 - 01/2014 | Not Completed

Senior School Certificate (Class XII), **CBSE Board**

2010 | Completed



Technical Skills

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | ReactJS | NodeJS | ExpressJS | MongoDB | Redux | DSA | GitHub



Soft Skills ■

Public Speaking | Managing Teams | Leadership | Business Acumen



Interests

Organizing Events | Swimming | **Programming Humour**

Summary & Objective

An enthusiastic Full Stack Web Developer, with 1300+ hours of coding experience. Knowledge of JavaScript, React JS, & Chakra UI. Aims to leverage knowledge & build world-class web applications while facilitating organization in achieving functional goals through Soft Skills.



Work Experience

Self Employed

2014 - 2018 | Chennai

- Organized Marketing & Sales events.
- Created a team of high-impact individuals & generated growth of 25% YOY.

2019 - 2022 | Mathura

• Lead teams of Marketing & Sales reps to market for-sale properties.



Projects

BatBuy.com 🛮

Batman Themed scalable eCommerce website that sells electronics, games & gadgets to batman fans. | Github 🛮

Features

- Landing Page with Animations and Carousels
- Authentication with Sign Up and Login Pages
- Product Page with Filters and Sorting
- Cart and Checkout Pages

Tech Stack:

JavaScript | ReactJS | Chakra UI | CSS | Render **Individual Project built in 6 days**

T-Track 「₹

A SaaS Product website that sells productivity software. | Github 🛮

Features

- Login, Signup, Product, and Checkout Pages
- Fully Responsive dedicated Admin Panel with server integration to store & fetch data.

Tech Stack:

HTML | SCSS | JavaScript | Heroku

Areas of Responsibility:

- Team Lead & Github Manager
- Developed Admin Panel with CRUD
- · Hosted Database on Heroku

A collaborative project developed by a team of Four in 6 days.